Ken Takahashi

Email: kent49771@gmail.com

Profile:

Fullstack/Blockchain Engineer.

Started from Java developer and moved to Fullstack engineer, worked for 12 years as software engineer.

Love programing with Golang, Node.js and React.js and my expertise is to design and implement APIs in backend side.

Recently, in the several blockchain companies, I had the opportunity to build/implemented Smart Contracts, NFTs, GameFi dApps, Market Place, and trading bots, which are emerging as major topics today, on blockchains such as Ethereum, Solana, and Flow.

I am confident that my experience and skills will help many customers succeed in their business and will do my best.

Thank you

Technical Skills:

Backend/Frontend Oriented

- Golang/Gin/Echo 7 years
- Node.js/Strapi 8 years
- Java/J2EE 6 years
- Php/Laravel 4 years
- React.js/React Native 6 years
- Vue.js 5 years
- Angular 1.x/2/5 3 years
- Elixir/Liveview 1 year
- Python/FastAPI 2 years

Blockchain Oriented

- ERC-20, ERC-721, ERC-1155
- Solidity
- Rust
- Cadence
- Hyperledger Blockchain
- Ethereum Blockchain
- Solana Blockchain

- Flow Blockchain

Others

- ibm cloud/AWS/Google cloud
- mysql/postgres/db2/mssql/oracle/mongodb
- docker/kubernates/Openshift/Jenkins/Gitlab CI
- firebase/kinvey
- Mqtt/Modbus/FIN/Opc-UA/HSMS etc

Languages:

English, Japanese

Education:

2005 – 2009 Bachelor's Degree, Kyoto University, Computer Science

Employment History:

Senior Full Stack/web3 Engineer, 1Kin, 2022.3 -

- dApp web3 integration(Next.js, web3)
- backend API implementation(Node.js, Strapi)
- Implement Smart Contract using Rust, Anchor, Solidity
- 3rd party integration alchemy, quicknode, sequence etc
- Universal wallet integration(EVM, Solana, Near, ImmutableX, Aptos)
- Game Collectible Claiming Platform(Next.js, node.js, AWS, grapfana, sentry, NewRelic, Redis)

Senior Backend/Blockchain Engineer, GigLabs, 2020.3 - 2022.2

- Developed GameFi smart contract on flow blockchain for Blocklete Golf Game Proshop(Cadence, Flow blockchain)
- Worked with backend part of GameFi(Node.js, postgres)
- Implemented EVM Smart contract and OpenBox from multiple NFTs(ERC 721, ERC 1155, Solidity, Hardhat), and Implemented dApp(React.js, web3)
- Implemented NFT raffle, Marketplace on Ethereum(Solidity)
- Implemented NFT raffle, dApps, Marketplace on Solana(Rust, Metaplex, Candy Machine)
- Implemented swap dApp(Uniswap, web3)
- Implemented Flashloan Trading bots(Solidity, web3, Ethereum, DEXs)

Full Stack Engineer, Childly, 2018.6 - 2020.2

- Improve feature of Dove Wallet backend/front(Vue.js, Node.js, Cryptocurrency)

- Implemented new backend for Dove Wallet based on Golang(Golang)

Lead Software Engineer, Room-Res, 2016.6 – 2018.5

- Implemented hotel booking agency backend/frontend/admin panel(Golang, React.js, Postgres, Laravel)
- Implemented Flight booking agency backend/frontend(Goalng, Vue.js)

Web Developer, ES Tech, 2012.6 - 2016.5

- Passed Java, SQL, Web courses
- Worked as web developer(Java, J2EE, php/Laravel)
- Implemented Delivery system(node.js, Angular)
- Implemented Mobile Apps using React-Native
- Implemented Java based ETL Solution